<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SLOTET/DEVLOG</title>
    <link>http://slotet.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SLOTET/DEVLOG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 Copyright Slotet. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 14:47:51 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://slotet.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SSS#8</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 14:47:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_8/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys. No videos or pics this week. I put a sprite of the character on the background of the sneak peek I wrote last week and moved it around. I was very happy with the result, but I can&amp;rsquo;t publish it on the internet because of copyright issues with the sprite I used as a placeholder. In any case, I can report that I have made some progress in the initial stages of graphic development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSS#7 - Prepare for next journey_01</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 10:58:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_7/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to update this devlog every Monday from now on. As you know, my progress is very slow, so I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to write much, but I thought it&amp;rsquo;s important to update even the most trivial things.
There is something I forgot to upload in my last post. A video of a camera test with defold-orthographic. I am considering using it in the future because it is easy to control the zoom from the script, although some adjustments are necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSS#6 - City and Nature</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_6/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone. I&amp;rsquo;d like to report on the progress I&amp;rsquo;ve made over the past week or so. I am still sketching over and over.
At first I had in mind the story of a man living in a city. Something like this(or please read previous post).
 However, I gradually realized that as a painter I did not enjoy painting cities.
   (lol, example of trying to emphasize a distinctive style and losing myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSS#5 - Prepare for next journey_00</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 14:33:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_5/</guid>
      <description>The following images are sketches for my next project.
          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSS#4 - Finally I made a piece of shit and the development log of it.</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_4/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys. I finally published a small game the past few days.
The Hollo Men on itch.io
As those of you who have played it will know (if you haven&amp;rsquo;t, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to play it, it&amp;rsquo;s a waste of time), this is an undeniably shitty game. I spent about a month on it, and I produced crap.
But I don&amp;rsquo;t regret it too much, because the requirements I set when I started this project had been met.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSS#3 - Ludum Dare 48: My first challenge to a game jam.</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_3/</guid>
      <description>On April 24 - 27, 2021, Ludum Dare 48 - An event to create a game in 72 hours - was held.
I was invited by my friend Thomas Olsson to participate in my first game jam as an pixel artist. I would like to share my overall impressions.
I think it would be helpful for artists who are interested in game jam but have never participated in it before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSS #2 - Considering about genre, and some sketches</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 08:07:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_2/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys. This is my second update.
I really wanted to do a weekly update, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it last week. It seemed to me that there was nothing worth showing to everyone. A friend said to me, &amp;ldquo;You should update your development blog every week. And see if it&amp;rsquo;s better to look good or to be forgotten by everyone.
Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s worth it to write that development isn&amp;rsquo;t going well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSS #1 - Introduce</title>
      <link>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 23:03:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slotet.com/blog/posts/sss_1/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,
Thank you for your interest in my work and for coming here.
On March 2, 2021, I posted a pixel art on twitter.
WIP #gamedev #Indiegamedev pic.twitter.com/BcddyRq7Xr
&amp;mdash; SLOTET (@SlotetStudios) March 2, 2021  This is the concept art for my game, which I drew little by little in between contract jobs. As many of you may know, this pixel art was seen by quite a few people. This is the first time in my life that I&amp;rsquo;ve done this, so I was very surprised, and more than anything, I was happy to see the warm response from you guys.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
